ibotoolbox.com 2013-05-02

# IBOTOOLBOX - free business marketing platform

|   |  

##  IBOtoolbox Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes IBOtoolbox's policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information. IBOtoolbox receives your information through our various web sites, SMS, APIs, services and third-parties ("Services"). When using any of our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Irrespective of which country that you reside in or create information from, your information may be used by IBOtoolbox in the United States or any other country where IBOtoolbox operates. 

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@ibotoolbox.com](mailto:privacy@ibotoolbox.com).

###  Information Collection and Use

**Information Collected Upon Registration:** When you create or reconfigure a IBOtoolbox account, you provide some personal information, such as your name, username, password, and email address. Some of this information, for example, your name and username, is listed publicly on our Services, including on your profile page and in search results. Some Services, such as search, public user profiles and viewing profiles, do not require registration.

**Additional Information:** You may provide us with additional information to make public, such as a short biography, your location, or a picture.  We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services or to market to you. You may unsubscribe from these messages by following the instructions contained within the messages or the instructions on our web site. If you email us, we may keep your message, email address and contact information to respond to your request. Providing the additional information described in this section is entirely optional.

**Profiles and other Public Information:** Our Services are primarily designed to help you share information with the world. Most of the information you provide to us is information you are asking us to make public. This includes not only the messages you post and the metadata provided with posts, such as when you posted, but also the blogs you create, the people you associate with, and many other bits of information. Our default is almost always to make the information you provide public but we generally give you settings to make the information more private if you want. Your public information is broadly and instantly disseminated. For example, your posts and blogs are searchable by many search engines and are immediately delivered to a wide range of users and services. You should be careful about all information that will be made public by IBOtoolbox.

**Log Data:** Our servers automatically record information ("Log Data") created by your use of the Services. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, the referring domain, pages visited, and search terms. Other actions, such as interactions with advertisements, may also be included in Log Data.

**Links:** IBOtoolbox may keep track of how you interact with links in Ads and posts across our Services including third party clients by redirecting clicks or through other means. We do this to help improve our Services, including advertising, and to be able to share aggregate click statistics such as how many times a particular link was clicked on.

**Cookies:** Like many websites, we use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services, but we do not require cookies for many parts of our Services such as searching and looking at public user profiles or lists. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. IBOtoolbox may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our Services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Services, and to improve our Services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

**Third Party Services:** IBOtoolbox uses a variety of services hosted by third parties to help provide our Services, such as hosting our various blogs and wikis, and to help us understand the use of our Services, such as Google Analytics. These services may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP request.

###  Information Sharing and Disclosure

Tip We do not disclose your private information except in the limited circumstances described here. 

**Your Consent:** We may share or disclose your information with your consent, such as when you use a third party web client to access your IBOtoolbox account.

**Service Providers:** We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us. We may share your personal information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to obligations mirroring the protections of this privacy policy.

**Law and Harm:** We may disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect IBOtoolbox's rights or property.

**Business Transfers:** In the event that IBOtoolbox is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. The promises in this privacy policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity.

**Non-Private or Non-Personal Information:** We may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information, such as your public Tweets or the number of users who clicked on a particular link (even if only one did).

###  Modifying Your Personal Information

If you are a registered user of our Services, we provide you with tools to access or modify the personal information you provided to us and associated with your account.

###  Our Policy Towards Children

Our Services are not directed to people under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at [privacy@ibotoolbox.com](mailto:privacy@IBOtoolbox.com). We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.

###  Changes to this Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at <http://ibotoolbox.com/privacy.aspx> If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you via an @IBOtoolbox update or e-mail to the email associated with your account. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

|    
---|---|---  
  
| **ADVERTISE YOUR BUSINESS**  IBOtoolbox provides the perfect platform to get your business noticed. With more than 300,000+ targeted visitors daily, our websites offer you a very targeted advertising medium.

IBOtoolbox and IBOsocial websites boast of more targeted traffic than any social networking site including FACEBOOK! Whether you want to target our members or the business prospects that come to our sites everyday, IBOtoolbox delivers! 

|  | **PRESS RELEASES**  While, our press release system has features that you will not find anywhere else on the Internet, most of our members use it because it's EASY! IBOtoolbox press releases are preformatted so all you have to do is fill in the content.

IBOtoolbox ensures your press releases are not only posted in a SEO friendly manner, but puts your information in front of thousands to read.   
  
---|---|---  
   
**LEAD GENERATION**  IBOtoolbox ws designed to be a work horse in respect to lead generation. Any contact form located inside the IBOtoolbox platform will generate a lead. IBOsocial profiles, squeeze pages, WallPlates, and unavailable live chat requests will all create lead. All leads created are available in your Contact Manager."  |  | **EVENTS SCHEDULING**  Schedule Events right on the dashboard or inside the CRM itself. Events will show up on the dashboard to keep you informed of upcoming events or call backs. The system will handle unlimited events and can be set with or without a CRM contact.   
   
**CONTACT MANAGER**  The IBOtoolbox contact manager is rich with features such as Email, Notes, History, email tracking(open), OPTIN/OPTOUT status, unlimited leads, unlimited groups, unlimited custom fields, it will even pull your contact up through Google Maps...

One look into the CRM and you know it is professionally put together! 

|  | **LIVE CHAT**  IBOtoolbox members enjoy free LiveChat services. Every IBOsocial Profile will have a built-in LiveChat system so you can communicate with your prospects without leaving the site.

With the new WallPlates, you can actually put IBOtoolbox Livechat service on your existing website with a single line of code! All for Free!   

**MEDIA SHARING**  IBOtoolbox media sharing through your IBosocial profile is easy, and setup for easy sharing. What makes this different than YouTube, is that you are sharing your business card (IBOsocial Profile) every time you share a video or picture

Every feature in the IBOtoolbox platform is specifically designed to promote your business. 

|  |  **BUSINESS SOCIAL NETWORK**  IBotoolbox members are able to mingle and "associate" with other Network Marketers from around the world in real time. Unlike Facebook and other Social network sites, IBOtoolbox is built for you the MARKETER!

IBOtoolbox is unlike any platform out there. It is guaranteed that by using this platform for free, you will be building your business!"   

**SALES TEAM BUILDING**  IBOtoolbox members will be able to build their sales teams by associating with other IBOtoolbox members. 

By interacting with other Network Marketers worldwide 24/7, you have the ability to bring experienced leaders into your organization as well as fresh new prospects!" 

|  |
